<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
    <!-- Portal Help Page: Step-by-step guide for customers -->
    <template id="portal_help_page" name="Helpdesk - How to Submit and Track Tickets">
        <t t-call="portal.portal_layout">
            <div class="container mt-4">
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-12">
                        <div class="mb-3">
                            <a href="/my/tickets" class="btn btn-sm btn-outline-secondary">
                                <i class="fa fa-arrow-left"/> Back to Tickets
                            </a>
                        </div>

                        <div class="card">
                            <div class="card-header bg-primary text-white">
                                <h3 class="mb-0"><i class="fa fa-info-circle"/> How to submit and track a support ticket</h3>
                            </div>
                            <div class="card-body">
                                <p class="lead">Follow these steps to create a ticket, provide details, and follow up until it's resolved.</p>

                                <ol class="list-group list-group-numbered mb-4">
                                    <li class="list-group-item">
                                        <strong>Prepare your details:</strong> Collect a clear subject, description of the issue, any screenshots or attachments, and your contact details (`Ticket Email` / `Ticket Phone`).
                                    </li>
                                    <li class="list-group-item">
                                        <strong>Create a ticket:</strong> Click <em>Create New Ticket</em> on the Tickets page or use the portal form. Choose the relevant <em>Category</em> and optionally the <em>Type</em>.
                                    </li>
                                    <li class="list-group-item">
                                        <strong>Email submissions:</strong> If you send the ticket via email, the system decodes the inbound message and displays it in the <em>Email</em> tab (read-only). The message is cleaned of special formatting for better readability.
                                    </li>
                                    <li class="list-group-item">
                                        <strong>What happens next:</strong> Agents will review and assign the ticket. If a ticket is moved to a <em>Rejected</em> stage, it is automatically reassigned to the team owner for review.
                                    </li>
                                    <li class="list-group-item">
                                        <strong>Follow up & resolution:</strong> Use the Messages area on the ticket to reply; you will receive updates in the portal. For escalation, request supervisor review in your reply or via the provided contact details.
                                    </li>
                                </ol>

                                <h5>Tips</h5>
                                <ul>
                                    <li>Attach files (screenshots, logs) to help engineers reproduce the issue faster.</li>
                                    <li>Use `Ticket Email` and `Ticket Phone` so agents can contact you directly if needed.</li>
                                    <li>Check the ticket <strong>Status</strong> on the Tickets page for progress updates.</li>
                                </ul>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
        </t>
    </template>
</odoo>
